iglobad.com 2017-06-22

# Privacy Policy - Responsive MultiPurpose HTML5 Template

You acknowledge and agree to be bound by the terms of our Privacy Policy. The Company reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Any changes to this policy will be effective immediately upon notice, which will be provided to you via e-mail or by posting the latest version on our Site. Your subsequent use of the Site be deemed acceptance of such changes. Be sure to review this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure familiarity with its most current version.  
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you as to what information may be collected from you when you visit our website (“the Site”) or when you become a Distributor, how such information will be used by the Company and/or other persons or entities, with whom such information may be shared, use and distribution of such information, your ability to edit, update, correct or delete such information and the security procedures that we have implemented to protect your privacy.

#### Types of data collected

When you subscribe to services of this web site, you must first complete a registration form. During registration, you are required to provide some information like name, address, email id, etc.  
Purpose for which data is used Data collected by the company may be used for following purposes:   
1\. The data is used to provide the member’s information about how reward points and commissions are calculated.  
2\. To address complaints and suggestion...  
3\. Meeting the requirements to make disclosure under requirements of any law binding on the Company.

#### Access or corrections to your information

The Company will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and accurate. You may review and update this information at any time. If you want to change any information provided by you, you may contact the Company so that the Company may update your information in its records or you may go online to the Company’s website and update your own information.

#### Security

The Company has taken reasonable measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and while the Company strives to protect your personal information, the Company cannot guarantee or warrant its complete security. The Company shall not responsible for any harm or suffering caused to you or any person as a result of a breach of confidentiality, with respect to your use of the Site or any information you transmit to the Site.

#### Data Integrity

Personal information will be kept in active files or systems as long as needed to meet the purposes for which it was collected or as required to perform the contractual relationship with the Distributor and his/her up-line, and the commercial relationship with the customer. The Company will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the information is accurate and complete.

#### Notice for Parents

Parents or guardians: The Company will help you guard your children's privacy. The Company encourages you to talk to your children about safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet. The Company site does not publish content that is targeted towards children and the Company will not collect Personally Information from them, knowingly. If the Company discovers personal information from a child through our Site, we will eliminate that information. You must be at least 18 years old to be a User or qualify as a Distributor to be on our Site.

#### Contact

If you have any concerns about our use of your information or about this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to support@iglobad.com or call 0041-456-3692. We will make every reasonable effort to address your concerns and remedy any problem you bring to our attention.
